<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui" xmlns:c="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.cellview.client">
	<ui:style>
		.centered {
			text-align: center;
			vertical-align: center;
			font-family: Rabio, sans-serif;
		}
		
		.Enter {
			font-size: 2em;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:ScrollPanel width="100%" height="100%">
		<g:Tree animationEnabled="true">
			<g:TreeItem text="Login/Registration/User Profile/Logout">
				<g:TreeItem text="Login using Google Account">
					<g:HTML>
						• You are asked to login using your Google account.
						<br />
						• The website will redirect to Google to login.
						<br />
						• Once you are logged in, you will be redirected back to the
						website.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Registration">
					<g:HTML>
						• Once logged in with your Google account; if it is the first time
						to you to use the system, you need to register with a new user
						name
						in the system.
						<br />
						• In the registration form, enter a username then click register.
						If the username was already taken by another user, you will be
						asked to enter another username.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Adding/Modifying Online Judges' accounts">
					<g:HTML>
						• Codemashup.com requires your login information of different
						online judges to be able to automatically submit solutions using
						your account.
						<br />
						• If you don't have accounts in any of the online judges, you can
						still use the features of Codemashup.com by submitting
						anonymously.
						<br />
						• You can modify your login information as well.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Sign out">
					<g:HTML>
						• If you want to sign out, simply click the sign out button.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>


			</g:TreeItem>


			<g:TreeItem text="Dealing with problems">




				<g:TreeItem text="View Problems List">
					<g:HTML>
						• A list of all problems is showed.
						<br />
						• The list contains problems aggregated from the different OJs.
						<br />
						• You can sort the Problem List by clicking on the list columns
						header.
						<br />
						• You can search in the problems list on any prefix in a
						particular
						column. (To be enhanced soon).
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View A Problem">
					<g:HTML>
						• To view a problem, select it from the problem list or enter the
						URL directly.
						<br />
						• The problem information contains:
						o Problem statement.
						<br />
						o Suggested problem categories (contributed from users)
						<br />
						o Submission area.
						<br />
						• You can also view the original problem page in the Online Judge.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Submit A Solution for A Problem">
					<g:HTML>
						• In the "view a problem", you have wrote a solution code for the
						problem and put it in the "submission area".
						<br />
						• Choose the language you used in the code.
						<br />
						• Select tags for the category of the problem.
						<br />
						• Choose whether you want your code publicly available or not.
						<br />
						• Click "submit".
						<br />
						• You will be redirected to the Submission result page.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View a submission result">
					<g:HTML>
						• You have just submitted a solution code, and got redirected to
						the “Submission results” page.
						<br />
						• The “Submission results” page contains: Submission date, Problem
						code, Judge Results (“AC”, “WA”, etc), The Execution Time, and The
						Memory Used By The executed code.
						<br />
					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>


			</g:TreeItem>



			<g:TreeItem text="Contests">


				<g:TreeItem text="Manage Contests">
					<g:HTML>
						• The Contest is locked by an access code. The Contest creator
						gives the access code to the contestants who will compete in the
						contest.
						<br />
						• Enter the contest information to create it.
						<br />
						• Select the problems to be added to the contest.
						<br />
						• Send the Contest name and the access code to the contestants who
						want to compete in the contest.
						<br />
						• The needed contest information:

						<pre> o Contest Name </pre>

						<pre> o Access Code</pre>

						<pre> o Start Date and Time</pre>

						<pre> o End Date and Time</pre>

						<pre> o Problem List (to choose contest problems from)</pre>

						• You can edit a contest, if you are the owner of it (created the
						contest).
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Join Contest">
					<g:HTML>
						• You can join a contest, if you know its access code.
						<br />
						• Choose a contest to join.The system then will ask you for the
						access code.
						<br />
						• Enter the access code, then, you will get into the contest (Good
						luck!)
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View Score Board">
					<g:HTML>
						• The score board is a table. The table columns stands for the
						problems. The table rows stands for the contestants The cells
						stands for the state of the problem to the contestant.
						<br />
						• The score board will be saved in the system after the contest
						has
						finished.
						<br />
						• The scoring system is similar to the ACM ICPC contest style.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View Contest Problems List">
					<g:HTML>
						• After joining a contest, in the score board, the columns headers
						are the problem list.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View A Problem in A Contest">
					<g:HTML>
						• Click on a problem in the problems list, the system will show
						you
						the problem page that contains "Problem Statement" and "Submission
						Area"
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="Submit A Solution for A Problem in a Contest">
					<g:HTML>
						• After selecting a problem from the problem list, you can submit
						a
						solution for the problem (in the problem page submission area).
						<br />
						• The judge result will be updated in the score board.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View Contest History">
					<g:HTML>
						• The saved "score board" can be viewed.
						<br />
						• You can view an ended contest.
						<br />
						• You can now see the saved "score board".
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



			</g:TreeItem>


			<g:TreeItem text="View Coders">

				<g:TreeItem text="View Coders List">
					<g:HTML>
						• You want to view the other coders that use this site.
						<br />
						• Open "View Coders".
						<br />
						• You get a list of all coders.The list contains: The coder
						Codemashup.com username, and each OJ user name (in a separate
						column).
						<br />
						• You can view a coder profile by clicking on his record in the
						list.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>



				<g:TreeItem text="View A Coder Profile">
					<g:HTML>
						• You want to view a coder's profile!
						<br />
						• Click on the coder's record in the list.
						<br />
						• The coder's profile has opened. The profile contains:
						<br />
						o The coder's Total number of submissions.
						<br />
						o The coder's number of AC submissions, WA submissions, and so on.
						<br />
						o The coder's last submissions and their results.
						<br />

					</g:HTML>
				</g:TreeItem>

			</g:TreeItem>
		</g:Tree>
	</g:ScrollPanel>

</ui:UiBinder> 